let's look at the answer to our miss
rate quiz in a well-designed cache we
want the hit rate to be as high as
possible and the Miss rate to be as low
as possible because the hit rate
determines how often do we have just a
hit latency and the Miss rate is how
often we have to pay the full memory
latency so we definitely want the hit
rate to be larger than the Miss rate we
definitely do not want the hitter to be
smaller than the Miss rate we don't want
them to be equal to each other because
that means that half of the time we're
going to memory we want to hit much more
than that
we want the hit rate to be almost 1
because that means that almost always we
are going to have a cache hit and we
definitely do not want the Miss rate to
be almost 1 because that means that we
are almost never hitting in our cache